http://www.dragonsabreast.com.au/privacy-policy

Dragons Abreast Australia - Privacy Policy
Celebrating 20 Years of Breast Cancer Recovery
Toggle navigation
Home About UsAbout DAAWhere it All BeganCorporateMeet the TeamRemember our AngelsForms and DocumentsGalleryDragons Abreast ShopOur AmbassadorsUseful LinksOur Groups News & ResearchLatest NewsResearchIn the LoopArchived NewsEventsFAQSContactDonate
Privacy Policy
Dragons Abreast Australia is strongly committed to protecting your privacy.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information.
Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you as a member of Dragons Abreast Australia. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.
Dragons Abreast Australia collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us how many people have visited our website, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth – they are 'anonymous'. Another example of collecting anonymous information is when Dragons Abreast Australia members or visitors to our site are invited to respond to surveys on our website. The surveys may ask you for demographic information such as your age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous. Many of the individuals who access our services are anonymous to us.
The second type of information that Dragons Abreast Australia collects is personal information. We will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address. With this information, Dragons Abreast Australia can provide a variety of personalised services e.g. member ID tags and newsletters.
Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond.
The only way we know something about you personally is if you or the coordinator of your group provides it to us, for example when you fill in a group membership form.
Use of anonymous information Dragons Abreast Australia automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of our website. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve how we do things to assure that the site is as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. Dragons Abreast Australia may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.
Dragons Abreast Australia will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. We will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.
Disclosure - There will be occasions where it will be necessary for Dragons Abreast Australia to disclose your personal information to third parties. We may be required by law to disclose the information, or we may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested, for example, if you require an ID card, we will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to print your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information.
Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside Dragons Abreast unless you have authorised us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online survey you may want to publish your name and email address.
Under no circumstances will Dragons Abreast Australia sell or receive payment for disclosing your personal information.
Whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as chat rooms or message boards, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the internet. This information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas.
Privacy Statement Personal information collected by Dragons Abreast Australia (DAA) is protected by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the 'Privacy Act'). Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you and includes sensitive and health information.
DAA follows the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act in handling personal information from clients/beneficiaries, business partners, donors, members of the public and DAA People (including members, volunteers, employees, delegates, candidates for volunteer work and prospective employees).
The primary purpose for collecting personal information from you is to provide services to vulnerable people, including planning, funding, monitoring and evaluating our services. The kind of information we collect will depend on your relationship with DAA (e.g. as a client, donor, business partner, employee, volunteer or member, on line user of the DAA website).
Your personal information may be used to:
provide you with a service
report to government or other funding bodies how funding is used
process your donation or purchase and provide receipts
communicate with you about how your donation is used or about DAA services, causes, events, products and services, which we believe may be of interest to you
respond to your feedback or complaints
answer your queries
It may also be used for:
any other specific purpose for which it was requested and which was advised to you
directly related purposes.
Please be assured that wherever possible DAA uses information in a de-identified form. Personal information will not be disclosed to third parties without your permission, except where permitted or required under the Privacy Act.
All personal, sensitive and health information collected will be securely stored by DAA and protected from unauthorised use or access, and all reasonable steps will be taken to ensure information is accurate and up-to-date. Our Privacy Policy also provides a process for requesting access to your personal information.
If you have any enquiries in relation to privacy or personal information please contact:
Phone: 1300 889 566Email: office@dragonsabreast.org.au PO Box 380Cannon Hill QLD 4170
ACN 104 261 029 ABN: 33 104 261 029
Home/Privacy Policy
Dragons Abreast Australia
Exclusive Dragons Abreast Australia promotional products.
Dragons Abreast Shop
Our Sponsors
Dragons Abreast Australia is sponsored by Specialised Therapeutics Australia, an international biopharmaceutical company with strategic focus and expertise in Australia, New Zealand and South East Asia.
With the highest professional and ethical standards, Specialised Therapeutics Australia commercialise therapies and technologies that uniquely fulfil the unmet medical needs of the community.
Quality and affordable sporting apparel. Provider of our DAA jackets, with a percentage of proceeds being donated to Dragons Abreast.
Amoena - supporting women’s confidence after breast cancer and throughout life.
As the world leader in research and manufacture of breast forms our story began 43 years and has expanded into 82 countries.
In recent years Amoena have incorporated cooling technology (Comfort+) into the breast forms. Lingerie has evolved from basic pocketed bra to high fashion French inspired lingerie.
Get in touch with Dragons Abreast Australia on 1300 889 566 or fill in our enquiry form
ENQUIRE NOW
GET IN TOUCH
Phone: 1300 889 566office@dragonsabreast.org.auPO Box 380Cannon Hill QLD 4170
Dominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe Islands
FijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltar
GreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuyanaHaitiHonduras
Hong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItaly
JamaicaJapanJersey (Channel Islands)JordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic Republic
LatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascar
MalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexico
Moldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNepal
NetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth Korea
NorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn
PolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRepublic of KosovoReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and Nevis
Saint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoa (Independent)San MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychelles
Sierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands
South KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerland
SyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzania
ThailandTimor-LesteTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks & Caicos IslandsUgandaUkraine
United Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City State (Holy See)VenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)Western SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Are you a breast cancer survivor?
Yes
No
DRAGONS ABREAST AUSTRALIA © 2015. All Rights Reserved. PRIVACY POLICY | REFUND POLICY | Web Development by Smart Multimedia
connect.move.live
